A Guide to the Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Clifton A. Woodrum Papers, 1979-1999
The Library of Virginia
42967
61 cu. ft. (134 boxes)
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
One box of privacy protected records is closed until 2075. Access to privacy protected records including but not limited to: criminal records, social security numbers, and medical records is restricted (public access and photoduplication) for 75 years after date of creation per Code of Virginia 42.1-78.
Acquisition Information
Gift of the Honorable Clifton A. Woodrum III, November 2006.
Biographical Information
Clifton 'Chip' A. Woodrum III of Roanoke, Virginia, was born in 1938 in Washington, D.C. He attended the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill and received his law degree from the University of Virginia. He was a delegate to the Democratic National Convention for Virginia in 1972 and served as Virginia Democratic state chair 1972-1976. He was elected to the Virginia State House of Delegates in 1980 and served until his retirement in 2004. His grandfather, Clifton A. Woodrum (1887-1950), served in the U.S. Congress from 1923 to 1945.
Scope and Content
Papers, 1979-1999, of Clifton 'Chip' A. Woodrum, former member of the Virginia House of Delegates in the 16th House District, encompassing Roanoke and Roanoke County. Included are legislative and project files, campaign files, press clippings and releases, speeches, and special media.
The papers contain information on specific legislation and topics such as crime, education, judicial selection, medical and health issues, state lottery, rights of women, and taxes. Included are resolutions and material relating to the budget and budget amendments, copies of Virginia House and Senate bills and resolutions, notes, memorandums, correspondence, newsclippings, press releases, reports, and studies. There is correspondence from constituents, colleagues, public interest groups, professional organizations, administration officials, and local government. Also included are internal memos and notes, drafts, reports and studies, and publications.
Woodrum was a spokesman for education, rights of women, and for a fairer tax code. He sponsored legislation in 1987 creating the Virginia Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program [H.B. 1216], a fund covering medical bills and other expenses for children who suffer disabling neurological injuries at birth. He also headed the Virginia Freedom of Information Advisory Council and pushed for access to government meetings and documents. He was an outspoken critic of the state's move toward electric utility deregulation. Of note are Woodrum's legislative efforts for Roanoke and the surrounding area, including the Roanoke city charter, education, redevelopment, Roanoke Valley consolidation, Hotel Roanoke, and the Roanoke Regional Woodrum Field Airport.
The collection was organized into three series, Numerical files, Legislation files, and Dated files. All three series contain the same type of materials, with Numerical files being the largest series that followed a system created by the office of Woodrum. The archivist attempted to provide descriptive folder titles in an effort to guide the researchers. Many of the folders are arranged by House Bill or House Joint Resolution number and a description of the bill follows the numbers.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Numerical files, 1979-1999
Series II: Legislation files, 1979-1999
Series III: Dated files, 1979-1999
Contents List
- Series I: Numerical files, 1979-1999., Extent: 33.3 cu. ft. (74 boxes) (Box 1-74)
  This series is organized in a numerical filing system established by Woodrums office. The system assigned a file number to either a state agency or topic and materials relating to that agency or topic were filed within that specific number.
  Agencies represented include the Dept. for the Aging, Dept. of Children, State Board of Elections, Dept. of Health, Dept. of Motor Vehicles, Dept. of Criminal Justice Service, Dept. of Taxation, District courts, Appropriations Committee, Courts of Justice, State Corporation Commission, Crime Commission, and the Governor of Virginia. Topics represented include the state budget, health care, appointment of judges, information technology, women's issues, voter registration, Democratic Party, victims rights, and gun control. Also included are materials on the establishment, construction, renovation, or maintenance of projects of local interest in Virginia's Sixteenth House district (Roanoke).
  Included are copies of amendments, correspondence, proposals, publications, notes, reports, and history various bills and amendments. Includes information regarding House Bill 1216 establishing the Birth Related Neurological Injury Compensation Act; establishment of the Hotel Roanoke Conference Center Commission Act; H.J.R. 100 Freedom of Information Act; Democratic caucus'; Total Action Against Poverty; Virginia State Lottery; and tax exemptions. Included is constituent correspondence regarding support or opposition to various legislation, such as the merger of Roanoke city and County, Roanoke city jail, and the building of a Jack Kent Cooke stadium in Alexandria. Also included are candidate contribution and expenditure forms, correspondence, memos, and financial disclosure forms.
  Arranged numerically by file number.
  - 1. Aging, Dept. of
    - [01.001] League of Older Americans, 1983-1989. (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - [01.002] Housing for the Elderly, 1987-1990. (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - [01.003] Silver Haired Legislation, 1987. (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - [01.004] General correspondence, 1987-1991. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - 2. Alcoholic Beverage Control, Dept. of
    - [02.001] Drinking Age, 1983-1985. (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - [02.004] Smith Mountain Lake ABC Store, 1986-1991. (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - [02.005] ABC- General correspondence, 1989-1994. (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - [02.008] H.B. 404 ABC laws and license, 1990. (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - [02.009] Beer Keg Registration, 1990-1991. (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - [02.011] H.B. 862 Mixed beverage licenses, 1992. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - 4. Attorney General, Office of.
    - [04.002] H.B. 1393 Cemeteries and columbarium's, 1986-1987. (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - [04.003] H.B. 67 Escheat, 1988. (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - [04.004] City Market Building, 1985. (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - [04.005] Name Change (Judge Coulter), 1987. (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - [04.007] Civil Digest/Law Digest, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - [04.009] Vehicular homicide/Involuntary manslaughter, 1988. (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - [04.010] Attorney General Legislative package, 1988. (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - [04.011] CADRE/RAYSAC (Roanoke Area Youth Substance Abuse Coalition), 1988-1989. (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - [04.013] Blind Bowlers Association, 1991. (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - [04.013-A] Opinion- Vacation of plats, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - [04.013-B] Opinion- Tenants by entirety- Nursing Homes Medical Assistance Service attachment of lien to home, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - 5. Aviation, Dept. of
    - [05.001] General correspondence, 1987-1988. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - 6. Children, Dept. of
    - [06.001] Child Day Care Council, 1987. (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - [06.002] H.B. 1189- Child Day Care Facilities, 1987. (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - [06.003] Child Care Programs, 1981-1991. (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - [06.004] Child Day Care- Quality Standards, 1987-1990. (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - [06.005] Bruce Rose Case, undated. (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - [06.007] H.B. 1171 Licensure of and employment in child-care programs, 1987. (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - [06.007] H.B. 709 Child care services and programs, 1988. (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - [06.008] H.J.R. 98 Screening adults who work with children- General, 1986. (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - [06.008] H.J.R. 98 Screening adults who work with children- Correspondence, 1986. (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - [06.008] Joint subcommittee studying screening of child-care personnel, 1986. (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - [06.008] Joint subcommittee studying screening of child-care personnel, 1986. (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - [06.008] Joint subcommittee studying screening of child-care personnel, 1986. (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - [06.008] Joint subcommittee studying screening of child-care personnel, 1986. (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - [06.010] Day Care Funding, 1987-1993. (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - [06.010-A] Child day care and development - Fund plan, 1997-1999. (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - [06.011] General correspondence, 1988-1990. (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [06.012] H.J.R. 127 Child abuse reporting and investigation, 1988. (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - [06.013] H.B. 709 Child care programs status file, 1988. (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - [06.014] Intergeneration day care, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 7. Commerce, Dept. of
    - [07.001] General correspondence, 1988-1989. (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - [07.002] National Association of Real Estate Appraisers, 1989-1990. (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - [07.002-A] H.B. 33, 34, 315 Appraisers, 1992. (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - [07.005] H.B. 1019 Practice of accountancy, 1987. (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - [07.006] Real estate brokers licensing, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - [07.006-A] H.B. 474 Regulations of real estate brokers, salespersons, rental location agents, and real estate board, 1990. (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - [07.007] Real estate transfer tax, 1989. (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - [07.008] Funeral and cemetery legislation, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - [07.009] Contractors, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - [07.009-A] Statue of repose, 1989-1991. (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - [07.009-B] S.B. 747 Pay back builders legislation, 1990. (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - [07.009-C] Home Builders Association, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - [07.009-D] H.B. 1034 Construction contracts and bids, 1992. (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - [07.009-E] H.J.R. 643 Design build study, 1995. (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - [07.009-E] H.J.R. 643 Design build study, 1995. (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - [07.009-E] H.J.R. 643 Design build study, 1995. (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - [07.009-F] H.B. 755 Escrow local governments construction retainage, 1997. (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - [07.010] Wine Franchise Act, 1989. (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - [07.011] Regulation of athlete agents, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 8. Community College System, Virginia.
    - [08.001] Virginia Western Community College, 1991. (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - [08.002] Correspondence, 1987-1990. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - 9. Conservation and Historic Resources and Preservation.
    - [09.001] Correspondence, 1987-1999. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - [09.002] Jefferson High School, 1989-1990. (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - [09.005] S.B. 514 Historic Preservation, 1992. (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - [09.007] Revolutionary war veterans cemeteries, 1998. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - 10. Corporation Commission, State.
    - [10.001] Correspondence, 1986-1987. (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - [10.002] Medical malpractice, 1986-1991. (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - [10.002] Medical malpractice, 1986-1991. (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - [10.002] Medical malpractice, 1986-1991. (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - [10.002-A] H.B. 1216 Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1987-1988. (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - [10.002-A] H.B. 1216 Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1987-1988. (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - [10.002-A] H.B. 1216 Neurological Injury Compensation Act, 1987-1988. (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, Staff study reports, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, Staff study reports, 1989. (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - [10.002-B] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 1216, 1989. (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - [10.002-C] Neurological Injury Act- Chairman of Study HJR 297, 1990. (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - [10.003] Tort reform, 1986-1987. (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - [10.003] Tort reform, 1986-1987. (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - [10.003] Tort reform, 1986-1987. (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - [10.004] H.J.R. 59 Uniform commercial code, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - [10.004] H.J.R. 59 Uniform commercial code, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - [10.004] H.J.R. 59 Uniform commercial code, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - [10.004] H.J.R. 59 Uniform commercial code, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - [10.004] H.J.R. 59 Uniform commercial code, 1988. (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - [10.004-A] H.J.R. 524 Uniform commercial code, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - [10.004-B] H.B. 2382 Uniform commercial code Article 5, 1996-1997. (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - [10.005] Bureau of Insurance, State Corporation Commission, 1986-1989. (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - [10.005] Bureau of Insurance, State Corporation Commission, 1986-1989. (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - [10.005] Bureau of Insurance, State Corporation Commission, 1986-1989. (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - [10.005-A] Health care costs, 1991. (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - [10.005-B] Mandated health insurance benefits, 1992. (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - [10.005-E] H.B. 1233 Insurance coverage of contraceptives, 1997. (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - [10.005-F] Long term care insurance, 1996. (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - [10.006] Public Service Ltd. Partnership, 1989. (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - [10.007] H.B. 1213 State Corporation Commission service of process, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - [10.008] H.B. 1356 State Corporation Commission power to compromise and settle, 1991. (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - 11. Virginia State Crime Commission.
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 10)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - [11.00] H.J.R. 225 Commission to study crime victim-witness services and S.J.R. 174 Commission to study the salaries of law-enforcement officers and other matters, 1986-1990. (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - [11.001] Fire arms- General correspondence, 1987-1990. (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - [11.001] Fire arms- General correspondence, 1987-1990. (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - [11.001-A] Non detectable firearms, 1989. (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - [11.001-B] H.B. 223 Firearm silencers, 1990. (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - [11.001-C] H.B. 1989 Firearms, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - [11.001-D] 1988 Gun bills, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - [11.001-E] National Riffle Association Municipal Authority, 1988. (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - [11.001-F] H.B. 291 Penalties Possession of loaded firearm by juvenile, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - [11.001-G] Firearms general, 1991. (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - [11.001-R] Gun control, 1995. (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - [11.002-A] Victims and witnesses of crime report, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - [11.002-C] Investigation and reports, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - [11.002-C1] H.B. 2018 Victim Impact Statements, 1993. (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - [11.003] Community diversion incentive program, 1987. (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - [11.004] H.B. 398 Indeterminate sentencing, 1988. (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - [11.005] General correspondence, 1987-1990. (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - [11.005] General correspondence, 1987-1990. (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - [11.006] Forensic Laboratories (DUI Blood Analysis Disposition), 1987-1990. (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - [11.006-A] H.B. 222 Blood breath testing, 1990. (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - [11.006-C] H.B. 1318 Release of an accused on bond or promise to appear, conditions of release, drug testimony, 1989. (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - [11.006-E] H.J.R. 60 Drug testing of arrestees study, 1988-1989. (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - [11.006-E] H.J.R. 60 Drug testing of arrestees study, 1988-1989. (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - [11.006-F] HB. 226 Admissibility of certificates, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - [11.006-G] DNA Testing, 1990. (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - [11.008-A] Crime Commission Studies, 1997. (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - [11.009] Jail issues, etc., 1985-1991. (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - [11.009] Jail issues, etc., 1985-1991. (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - [11.009] Jail issues, etc., 1985-1991. (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - [11.009] Jail issues, etc., 1985-1991. (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - [11.009-A] Jail overcrowding, 1990-1991. (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - [11.009-B] Jail location, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - [11.009-C] Women's Correctional issues, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - [11.009-D] Local Juvenile Detention Home Funding, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - [11.010-B] Privatization, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - [11.010-G] Virginia Dept. of Corrections Community Corrections reports, 1997-1999. (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - [11.012] Convenience store safety, 1990-1991. (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - [11.012-A] Public protection while on business property, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - [11.013] Virginia State Sheriffs Association, 1988-1993. (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - [11.015] Virginia State Crime Commission, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - [11.015-B] Virginia State Police, campaigning, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - [11.016] Study, access ton confidential juvenile records, 1992. (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - [11.017] S.B. 852 Appointment of counsel in capital cases, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - [11.018] Funding, 1989-1990. (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - [11.019-A] H.B. 1308 Asset Forfeiture Distribution, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - [11.019-A] H.B. 1308 Asset Forfeiture Distribution, 1991. (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - [11.020] Pre and post-incarceration services, 1993. (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - [11.021] H.J.R. 147 Ritual Crime Task Force study, 1990. (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - [11.021-A] Study of cults, 1990-1991. (Box 14, Folder 19)
    - [11.023] S.J.R. 14 Drug trafficking, 1990. (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - [11.023-A] Drug trafficking, 1989. (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - [11.023-A] Drug trafficking, 1989. (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - [11.024] Police auxiliary, 1988. (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - [11.025-A] Law enforcement compensation, 1986-1990. (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - [11.025-B] Crime Commission, 1993. (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - [11.026-A] Probation, parole salaries, 1989-1990. (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - [11.028] Crime bills, 1989. (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - [11.029] Legislative proposals, 1992. (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - [11.030] H.J.R. 283 Handicapped inmates State Crime Commission, 1989. (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - [11.030] H.J.R. 283 Handicapped inmates State Crime Commission, 1989. (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - [11.030-A] Handicapped inmates education, 1992. (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - [11.031] H.B. 685 Juvenile transportation, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - [11.031-A] Transportation of mentally ill persons, 1991. (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - [11.032] Arson, 1993. (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - [11.033] Death penalty, 1989. (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - [11.033-A] Death penalty by injection, 1991. (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - [11.033-B] H.B. 1364 Death penalty for juveniles, 1991. (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - [11.037] H.B. 225 Special education of children incarcerated, 1990. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - [11.038] Manslaughter,. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - [11.041] Drug Court Program,. (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - [11.042] Virginia Commission on Youth,. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - [11.046] Child pornography proposed legislative changes, 1999. (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - [11.047] Executive subcommittee,. (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - 12. Economic Development, Dept. of
    - [12.001] Tourism, 1988-1991. (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - [12.002] Correspondence, 1986-1987. (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - [12.002] Correspondence, 1986-1987. (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - [12.003] Imaging Center Competition of other industries, 1991. (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - [12.004] Regional partnership, 1987. (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - [12.006] Frontier Culture Museum of Virginia, 1988. (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - [12.007] General correspondence, 1987-1991. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - [12.008] Virginia Horse Center 1987. (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - [12.009] George C. Marshall Foundation, 1988. (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - [12.010] Center for Innovative Technology, 1989. (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - [12.011] Fifth Planning District Commission, 1989-1991. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - [12.012] Welcome Centers, 1989-1990. (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - [12.013] Mill Mountain 200, 1987-1990. (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - [12.014] New Century Council, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - [12.015] Jefferson National Forest, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - [12.016] Disney Company theme park Prince William County, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - [12.016] Disney Company theme park Prince William County, 1994. (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - 13. Education, Dept. of
    - [13.001] General correspondence, 1986-1991. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - [13.001] General correspondence, 1986-1991. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - [13.001] General correspondence, 1986-1991. (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - [13.002] Elected school boards. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - [13.003] Literary funds. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - [13.006] Virginia tuition grants, 1986-1989. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - [13.007] School opening date, 1987-1991. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - [13.008] Virginia State Library, 1987-1989. (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - [13.008-A] Public libraries, 1992. (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - [13.009] Center for graduate studies, 1987. (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - [13.009-A] Ft. Lewis school letters, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - [13.009-B] Bent Mountain school letters, 1990. (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - [13.010] Teachers' education, 1987-1991. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - [13.011] Proposed revisions to standards of quality of public schools in Virginia, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - [13.012] Non resident tuition, 1988. (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - [13.014] Education symposium, 1989. (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - [13.015] Virginia Tech correspondence, 1990-1991. (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - [13.016] North Carolina tuition, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - [13.017] George Mason University, 1990. (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - 14. Elections, State Board.
    - [14.001] Campaign files (contribution and expenditure forms), 1987. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - [14.001] Campaign files (contribution and expenditure forms), 1987. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - [14.001] Campaign files (contribution and expenditure forms), 1987. (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - [14.001] Campaign files (contribution and expenditure forms), 1987. (Box 20, Folder 10)